hollywoodnews.com 2019-04-21

# PRIVACY | HollywoodNews.com

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the Hollywood News®, HollywoodNews.com. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to https://hollywoodnews.com (“Site”) and the Hollywood News® branded and related products and services that are owned and operated by Hollywood Network, Inc. This Policy describes how HollywoodNews.com collects, uses, shares, and protects information collected on our Site or through our products and services, as well your choices regarding use, access, and correction of your personal information. 

Your privacy is very important to us. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security.

**UPDATED TO REFLECT THE NEW EU, GDPR: Effective Date May 24, 2018**

**Personally-Identifiable Information**  
Hollywoodnews.com receives specific data about its Site visitors when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you certain types of information.

**Non Personally-Identifiable (Generic) Information**  
Hollywoodnews.com gathers some generic information automatically. Generally, this information does not reveal the identity of the visitor. It usually includes information about the Internet address assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of visitors, and the Hollywoodnews.com sites visited. We may automatically collect certain information through the use of cookies and other tracking technologies. Please see our Cookies & Other Tools section below to learn more about such tracking tools.

**Information Collection and Use**

Companies are the sole owners of the information collected on their sites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Companies collect information from our users at several different points on our websites.

**Registrations**

Users are provided with the option of using registration forms on our sites, where users can provide their contact information (such as name and email address), so we can contact the user about the services on our sites and/or provide news and information for which they have expressed interest. We do not share, trade, sell or disclose this contact information to others.

**Orders**

We request information from the user on our order forms, if any. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers’ orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user.

Advertisers, partners and sponsors may use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

**Sharing**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners, sponsors and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

If we partner with another party to provide specific services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services to the user when the user signs up for them. We expressly disclaim responsibility for information users provide once it has been transmitted to the third party on behalf of the user to provide the services or products the user has requested.

**Links**

Companies’ websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Companies are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our websites.

**Third-Party Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Newsletters, Bulletins, Special Offers, Etc.**

If a user wishes to receive our newsletters, bulletins or special offers, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We do not share, sell, trade or disclose that information to anyone, except if required in special cases (see Special Cases below). Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Users may unsubscribe or request to be removed from our mailing lists at any time by using online commands that we have created for that purpose.

**Online Voting, Surveys, Contests**

From time-to-time our sites may request information from users via online voting polls, surveys or contests. Participation in these voting polls, surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We expressly disclaim responsibility for information users provide to third parties, such as advertisers, partners, sponsors, or non-Companies websites, where services such as these are provided and information requested from the user.

**Security**

Our websites take every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the websites, we try our best to protect that information both online and off-line.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by phone, fax, mail or email.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Special Cases**

It is our policy not to use or share the personal information about visitors or members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, the Companies may disclose personal information about visitors or members, or information regarding your use of the services or websites provided by Companies, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including to satisfy laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating acceptable use policies or other user policies; to operate our services properly; or to protect Companies and their visitors, members or users.

**Public Forums**

Please remember that any information you may disclose in or on our directories, bulletin boards, listserv forums, or other public areas of our websites becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas. You should also exercise caution when contacting others who have posted information in such areas. You are solely responsible for any dealings you have with others via public information posted by you or by them.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you may contact:

Customer Service  
Legal Matters  
HollywoodNews.com  
433 N. Camden Drive, Suite 600  
Beverly Hills, CA 90210  
info@hollywoodnews.com  
Phone: 310-887-1444 – Fax: 310-288-0060
